Guide to the Stanford University Print Collection SC1039
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Prints
  - Sketches of arms and flags of schools of Stanford University, bo Prof. Eric Hutchinson. Sketches of arms, flags, and crests for Stanford University., 1967; P047
    - School of Education Coat of Arms; matted sketch on cardboard (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Graduate School of Business Coat of Arms; matted sketch on cardboard (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Graduate Division Coat of Arms; matted sketch on cardboard (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - University Coat of Arms; matted sketch on cardboard (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Paoletti, A.E. Original water colors of mosaics in front of Stanford Museum. "These water colors by A.E. Paoletti are the originals from which Dr. Salviati made the mosaics.. .", P048; water colors; 7 3/4 x 3 3/4 or 5 (Box A1)
    Museum - building; Paoletti, A. E.
  - Orr, Louis. Stanford University, eight etchings. 10/20/88 - Six etchings framed: 3 are Bruce Jones' office C.Director's office Green East; 3 are boxed and stored in Bender Room. (2 left in box B2.), 1930; P049 (Box B2)
    3 framed ones found in 3sort when dept. moved back to Green West 5/99, not sure if these are represented above or are additional. They have been boxed separately.
    campus views; Orr, Louis; Orr, Louis
  - "At the Play" respectfully inscribed to the Wealth, Enterprise and Beauty of California by their faithful friend, Frederick Marriott. Supplement to the July 19, 1879 San Francisco Newsletter, reissued, August, 1883. Lithograph by Britton and Rey. Also, an article from the San Francisco Sunday Chronicle, April 9, 1961, describing the print, a black-and-white print of the lithograph, and a key to the lithograph., July, 1879; P050; 25 x 38 (Box D1)
    Contents: Reprint from SF News Letter July 18, 1896 in B boxes; Reprint from 1961 SF Chronicle in C boxes
  - Hill, Thomas A. The driving of the last spike. Color reproduction and key., P051; 19 x 27 1/2 (Box D1)
    Gold Spike.; Hill, Thomas A.
  - Diploma of James Freeman Jenness, B.A., 1892, Stanford University. Parchment with seal and ribbon., P055; diploma; 15 1/2 x 21 (Box D1)
    Jenness, James Freeman; Students
  - Masonic Club of Stanford University. Charter signed by officers and 25 members., 25-Oct-20; P056; 30 x 22 (Box MC)
    Masonic Club
  - Testimonial to Mrs. Stanford on the occasion of the laying of the cornerstone of the Gymnasium, with signatures of student body., 1902; P057; 23 x 18 (Box C2)
  - Stanford University war service record. "Tabulations be classes showing number in Army, Marines, & Navy segregated according to grade.", 1-Apr-19; P060; 35 1/2 x 25 1/2 (Box MC)
    World War, 1914-1918.
  - Certificate of distinction... awarded by the War Department to Stanford University for the training of soldiers in the Army Specialized Training Program during World War II., P061; 12 x 15 1/2 (Box B2)
    World War, 1939-1945 -- Army Specialized Training Program
  - Hoernes, T.K. (?) Interior of the Memorial Church., P070; 22 x 16 (Box C2)
    Memorial Church; Hoernes, T.K.
  - Stanford University. All campus buildings sketched, roads labelled., 1967 (?); P075; 19 x 25 (Box D2)
    Campus, Map of - 1967(?)
  - The Stanford Campus as seen by your A.V.C. chapter. American Veteran's Committee broadside announcing its activities., 1947; P100a; 9 x 11 (Box A2)
    American Veterans Committee
  - Stanford University tour for visitors attending the American Library Association Convention. Map is a reproduction of Arthur Lites' 1945 map of Stanford., 1947 (?); P100b (Box A2)
  - Stanford Alumni Association. Memorial on the death of Jane L. Stanford., 4-Mar-05; P101; 11 x 8 1/2 (Box A2)
    Aumni Association - 1905
  - Pastor's Association of Palo Alto. Memorial on the death of Jane L. Stanford., 20-Mar-05; P102; 10 x 8 (Box A2)
  - National Society of Colonial Dames of California. Resolution on the death of Jane L. Stanford, sent to Mr. Charles Lathrop. Matted., 16-Mar-05; P103; 6 x 9 (Box A2)
  - Faculty and Students of the Santa Clara High School. Resolution on the death of Jane L. Stanford., 21-Mar-05; P104; 10 1/2 x 8 1/2 (Box A2)
  - Women's Auxiliary of the Society of California Pioneers. Memorial on the death of Jane L. Stanford., 19-Mar-05; P105; 6 1/2 x 10 1/2 (Box A2)
  - Regents of the University of California. Resolution on the death of Mrs. Stanford., 18-Mar-05; P106; 10 x 16 (Box B3)
  - Humboldt Club. Resolution on the seath of Jane L. Stanford., P107; 14 x 11 (Box A2)
  - Cooley, W.W. "A Tribute", poem on the death of Jane L. Stanford., P108; 14 x 9 (Box A2)
    Cooley or Codey???
    Cooley, W.W.
  - Sheltering Arms Society. Resolution on the death of Jane L. Satnford., 20-Mar-05; P109; 17 x 14 (Box B3)
  - Santa Clara Women's Club. Resolution on the death of Jane Lathrop Stanford., 17-Mar-05; P110; 9 1/2 x 8 (Box A2)
  - Century Club of California. Resoultions on the death of Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford., P111; 9 1/4 x 8 1/2 (Box A2)
  - The Westminster Child Study Circle. Resolution on the death of Mrs. Stanford., 22-Mar-05; P112; 9 1/2 x 7 1/2 (Box A2)
    Stanford Jane L. - resolutions on the death of
  - Native Daughters of the Golden West - Alta Parlor No. 3. Resolution on the death of Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford., 11-Mar-05; P113; 10 1/2 x 8 1/2 (Box A2)
  - Mills College. Resolution on the death of Mrs. Jane L. Stanford., 20-Mar-05; P114; 11 x 8 (Box A2)
  - Board of Supervisors of Santa Clara County. Resolution on the death of Mrs. Jane L. Stanford., 20-Mar-05; P115; 10 3/4 x 8 3/4 (Box A2)
  - Faculty of the University of the Pacific. Resolution on the death of Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford., 16-Mar-05; P116; 13 1/2 x 10 (Box A2)
  - Forum Club. Resolution on the death of Jane Stanford., 14-Mar-05; P117; 7 x 8 1/2 (Box A2)
  - San Jose Women's Club. Memorial resolution on the death of Jane Lathrop Stanford., 4-Mar-05; P118; 14 x 10 (Box A2)
  - The Student Body of the Leland Stanford Junior University. Memorial on the death of Mrs. Stanford., P119; 14 x 10 1/2 (Box A2)
    Students - 1905
  - Stanford University Club of Portland. Memorial on the death of Mrs. Jane L. Stanford, 2-Mar-05; P120; 10 1/2 x 12 1/2 (Box A2)
    Alumni Association Clubs - Portland, 1905
  - Alumni and Students of Stanford University residing in the territory of Hawaii. Resolution on the death of Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford., 7-Mar-05; P121; 16 x 10 1/2 (Box B3)
    Alumni Association Clubs - Hawaii, 1905
  - Grand International Auxiliary of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Mrs. Leland Stanford Division, no. 106. Resolution on the death of Jane Lathrop Stanford., 16-Mar-05; P122; 10 1/2 x 16 (Box B3)
  - Board of Directors of the Home of Benevolence of San Jose. Memorial on the death of Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford., 21-Mar-05; P123; 20 1/2 x 5 1/2 (Box C2)
  - The Stanford Club of San Jose. Resolutions on the death of Mrs. Jane L. Stanford., P124; 20 3/4 x 5 1/4 (Box C2)
    Stanford Alumni Club -- San Jose, 1905
  - The California State Association. Resolutions on the death of Mrs. Stanford., 15-Apr-05; P125; 20 x 8 3/4 (Box C2)
  - California Club of California. Resolutions on the death of Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford., 22-Mar-05; P126; 20 1/4 x 8 (Box C2)
  - Alumni Club of Los Angeles - Class of '97. Resolutions on the death of Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford., P127; 20 1/4 x 8 1/2 (Box C2)
    Stanford Alumni Club -- Los Angeles, 1905
  - Citizens of California residing in the territory of Hawaii. Tribute to the memory of Mrs. Jane L. Stanford., 6-Mar-05; P128; 23 1/2 x 8 1/2 (Box C2)
  - Pioneers of California, Santa Clara County. Memorial to Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford., P129; 23 1/4 x 8 (Box C2)
  - Patrons of Husbandry, Lincoln Grange #318. Memorial on the death of Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford., P130; 22 x 8 (Box C2)
    Stnaford, Jane L. - resolutions on the death of
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, California Alpha. Resolution on the death of Jane Lathrop Stanford addressed to David Starr Jordan., 18-Mar-05; P131; 21 3/4 x 8 1/2 (Box C2)
    Fraternities - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1905
  - Association of Pioneer Women of California. Memorial on the death of Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford., 5-May-05; P132; 23 x 18 (Box C2)
  - Former Students of Stanford University, Assembled at Los Angeles. Resolution on the death of Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford., 6-Mar-05; P133; 23 x 17 (Box C2)
    Stanford Alumni Club -- Los Angeles
  - Golden Gate Kindergarten Association. Resolution on the death of Mrs. Leland Stanford., 13-Mar-05; P134; 22 x 18 (Box C2)
  - Mayor and Common Council of the city of San Jose. Resolutions on the death of Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford., 13-Mar-05; P135; 22 x 18 (Box C2)
  - Stanford Club of San Francisco. Memorial on the death of Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford., P136; 17 1/2 x 15 (Box C2)
    Stanford Alumni Club -- San Francisco, 1905
  - Stanford Club of Puget Sound. Memorial on the death of Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford., 8-Mar-05; P137; 20 x 12 (Box B3)
    Stanford Alumni Club -- Puget Sound, 1905
  - Native Sons of the Golden West, Monterey, California, in the Grand Parlor. Resolutions on the death of Jane L. Stanford., P138; 25 x 18 (Box D2)
  - The Board of Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior University. Memorial on the death of Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford., 18-Mar-05; P139; 28 x 22 (Box D2)
    Trustees, Board of - 1905
  - Newcomer, Alphonso G. Poem dedicated to Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford on her seventieth birthday., 25-Aug-05; P140; 10 3/4 x 11 1/4 (Box A2)
  - Hebrew Home for the Aged Disabled. Certificate of honorary membership for Mrs. Leland Stanford., January 11, 1897; P141; 17 3/4 x 13 3/4 (Box B3)
  - The Olympic Club. Certificate as a gift of thanks for Bonds donated by Mrs. Jane Stanford., P142; 16 3/4 x 11 1/2 (Box B3)
  - The Stanford Alumni Club of San Francisco. Certificate of support of Mrs. Stanford's intention to turn over the control of University affairs to the Board of Trustees., 14-Feb-03; P143; 19 x 15 1/2 (Box B3)
    Stanford Alumni Club -- San Francisco, 1903
  - Board of Directors of the Southern Pacific Company. Memorial on the death of Leland Stanford., June 29, 1893; P144 a,b,c; 21 1/2 x 13 1/2 (Box C2)
  - Board of Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior University. Memorial on the death of Leland Stanford., P145; 17 1/2 x 11 (Box C2)
    Trustees, Board of - 1893
  - Employees of the Southern Pacific Company. Resolutions on the death of Leland Stanford., June 22, 1893; P146; 19 3/4 x 15 1/2 (Box C2)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Orange Grove Division #5. Resolutions on the death of Leland Stanford., June 27, 1893; P147; 19 3/4 x 16 (Box C2)
  - Hurley, W.J. and the Reverand Andrew Desmond. Poem "In Memoriam" dedicated to Leland Stanford., P148; ink on satin; 23 x 20 (Box C4)
  - Republican State Convention. Memorial on the death of Leland Stanford., June 21, 1894; P149; 25 x 20 (Box C4)
  - Employees of the Southern Pacific Shops at Sacramento. Memorial on the death of Leland Stanford., P150; 28 x 22 (Box D2)
  - Jordan, David Starr. "Ecce Homo!" poem to the memory of Leland Stanford. Sent to Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford on her seventieth birthday., August 25, 1898; P151; 28 3/4 x 23 3/4 (Box C4)
    Jordan, David Starr, 1851-1931
  - San Francisco Art Association. Certificate of Life Membership for Leland Stanford., July 23, 1872; P152; 15 1/4 x 19 (Box C4)
    San Francisco Art Association - 1872
  - Garfield Monument Association of the Pacific Coast. Certificate attesting to the Honorable Leland Stanford's contribution to the fund., Sept. 24, 1881; P153; 20 x 15 (Box C4)
    Garfield Monument Association of the Pacific Coast - 1881
  - Native Sons of the Golden West, Mission Parlor, No. 38. Certificate honoring the Stanfords for their endowment Stanford University., Nov 18, 1885; P154; 21 x 14 (Box C4)
    Native Sons of the Golden West, Mission Parlor, No.38
  - Teachers of the Public Schools of Oakland. Certificate of appreciation to Leland Stanford for his contribution to education in California., P155; 16 x 22 1/2 (Box C4)
    Teachers of the Public Schools of Oakland
  - Geographical Society of California, San Francisco. Certificate of life membership for Leland Stanford., Feb 1, 1892; P156; 13 x 16 1/2 (Box B3)
    Geographical Society of California, San Francisco
  - Athens University, Tennessee. Certificate of honorary Doctor of Laws, presented to Leland Stanford., 1888; P157; 16 3/4 x 19 3/4 (Box B3)
    Athens University, Tennessee
  - Board of Directors of the Central Pacific Railroad. Resolution on the death of Leland Stanford., June 29, 1893; P158; 34 x 26 1/2 (Box map case)
  - Native Sons of the Golden West, Parlor #1. Certificate honoring Senator and Mrs. Leland Stanford for endowing the University., Dec 17, 1885; P159; 38 x 29 (Box MC)
    Native Sons of the Golden West, California, Parlor No.1
  - Rector, Wardens, and Vestry of Grace Church, San Francisco. Resolutions on the death of Leland Stanford, Junior., Nov 26, 1884; P160; 19 1/2 x 16 (Box B3)
  - Stanford University Library. Drawing of the library (architect's proposed sketch), unsigned., 1906; P161; ink drawing; 19 1/2 x 10 (Box C4)
    Libraries
  - Pedigree of Iran Alto. Dedicated to the memory of Leland Stanford and his theory of "fusing" thoroughbred and trotter blood., circa 1893; P162; 25 x 29 (Box MC)
  - Sketch of Palo Alto, Leland Stanford Junior University. Drawn by H. Boyd, from the City Argus, December, 1888. Depicts Mr. Stanford surrounded by Stock Farm and University scenes., Dec, 1888; P163; 29 x 14 inches (Box D2)
    Encapsulated copy found in unprocessed prints (6/2006).
    Stanford, Leland - cartoons about; Boyd, H.
  - Advertiser by Electioneer and __________., P164; 11 x 15 1/2 (Box B3)
  - Parts of Leland Stanford Junior's sketch book. Includes sketch of crude steam engine, sail boats, and locomotive engine., circa 1875; P165; pencil, pen on paper; varied (Box C4)
    Stanford, Leland
  - Students for a Democratic society. Nine demands posted on the door of the President's office, concerning Stanford Research Institute., Oct 14, 1868; P166 (Box A3)
    Students for a Democratic Society - 1968
  - Palo Alto. Thoroughbred chart and background chart of the stallion, Palo Alto. (1882-1892), P167 (Box A3)
  - Electioneer. Thoroughbred chart and history of the trotter, Electioneer., P168 (Box A3)
  - First annual encampment of the second brigade, C.M. Brigadier General Ellis, commanding. Reviewed by his excellency, Governor Stanford. Brigade drill and Samfight, October 14, 1863. From nature and on stone, printed by L. Nagel., Oct 14, 1863; P169; 20 x 30 (Box MC)
    Grob, T.
  - Stanford, Leland Jr. Eleven pencil sketches drawn by Leland Stanford, Jr., P170 (Box C4)
  - Republic Francaise. Ministere du Commerce, De L'Industrie Des Postes Et Des Telegraphes Exposition Universelle de 1900... Medaille de Bronze a Leland Stanford's Vina Ranch Vinyard., P171; 18 x 22 (Box C4)
    Vina Ranch (Calif.)
  - California Legislature, fifteenth session. Concurrent resolution... to Leland Stanford for the able, upright, and faithful manner in which he has discharged his duties as the governor of the state of California., Dec. 15, 1863; P172; 24 x 30 (Box MC)
  - Board of Manufacturers and Employers of California. Directors resolution on the death of Leland Stanford., 28-Jun-08; P173; 17 x 13 (Box B3)
  - Olympic Club of San Francisco. Resolution on the death of Jane L. Stanford., 6-Mar-05; P174 (Box B3)
  - Pacific Improvement Company. Resolution on the death of Jane L. Stanford., 1-Mar-05; P175 (Box B3)
  - National Society of the Daughters of the American Revolution. Membership certificate #605 issued to Jane Lathrop Stanford., Jan 30, 1892; P176 (Box B3)
  - Republique Franciase Ministere du Commerce de L'Industrie, des Postes et des Telegraphes Exposition Universaille de 1900. Medaille D'Or a Monsieur D.S. Jordan, a Stanford., P177 (Box D2)
    Jordan, David Starr
  - Electronic Research Laboratory. Stanford University, Stanford California. Organizational chart. "J.L.G."(?), 14-Dec-55; P178; blueprint; 24 x 30 (Box MC)
    Electrical Engineering, Dept. of
  - Ayrshire Farm - 1242 Acres. Residence of Peter Coutts, esq. Mayfield. Santa Clara County, California., P179; 10 x 12 1/2 (Box A3)
    Coutts, Peter - Ayrshire farm; Ayrshire Farm
  - Central Pacific Railroad Jupiter (locomotive) by Harlan Hiney. Golden West Books, San Marino., 1970; P180; color lithograph; 12 x 15 (Box B3)
    locomotive; Central Pacific Railroad; Stanford, Leland - Central Pacific Railroad; Hiney, Harlan
  - Union Pacific R.R. No. 119 by Harlan Hiney. Golden West Books, San Marino., 1970; P181; color lithograph; 12 x 15 (Box B3)
    Union Pacific Railroad; Hiney, Harlan
  - The Leland Stanford Junior University, at Palo Alto, California. Drawn by Hughson Hawley. From Harper's Weekly, October 3, 1891, p. 753., P182; colored lithograph; 11 1/4 x 16 1/4 (Box B3)
    Stanford in Periodicals;; Architecture - Campus Plan; Hawley, Hughson
  - Senator Leland Stanford's farm at Palo Alto, and the proposed university. From Harper's Weekly, April 21, 1888, p. 289., P183; 10 x 15 (Box B3)
    c. 2 from 2008-200.
    Stanford in Periodicals;; Architecture - Campus Plan
  - Barnes, Gertrude Jameson. Residence of Doctor Lee from Loggia of Doctor Mosher., 1931 or 1932?; P184; 9 1/2 x 12 (Box A3)
    faculty housing; Barnes, Gertrude Jameson
  - Hoover, Herbert. "For president, Herbert Hoover; for vice president, Charles Curtis." Campaign poster. Chicago., 1928; P185; 18 x 24 (Box C4)
    Hoover, Herbert; Politics
  - Pi Sigma Alpha. Graham H. Stuart Award (1952-1960)., P186; 14 x 17 (Box B3)
    Pi Sigma Alpha
  - Austin, Charles Dalton. Drawing by Charles Dalton Austin, approximately 1901; architect with Shepley, Rutan and Coolige. (Inner Quad), P187; 13 3/4 x 17 1/2 (Box B3)
    Austin, Charles Dalton; Austin, Charles Dalton
  - Austin, Charles Dalton. Water color and pencil sketch of an arch., P188; 7 1/2 x 10 (Box A3)
  - Pi Sigma Alpha. Charter for Eta chapter, Stanford University, February 9, 1926., Feb. 9, 1926; P189; 11 1/2 x 16 (Box B3)
  - Phi Beta Kappa. Charter of Phi Beta Kappa ... Beta chapter., Sept. 7, 1904; P190; 13 1/2 x 20 1/2 (framed)
    Phi Beta Kappa
  - Strand, Paul. Seventeen photographic views of Stanford campus., P191; 20 x 16 (Box B3)
    Campus views; Fraternities; Strand, Paul; Strand, Paul
  - "How it looks to the people.. .", P192; 12 x 17 (Box B3)
  - National Autonomy University of Mexico. "On action of the members of its student body send to Stanford University a cordial greeting.", P193; 9 1/2 x 13 1/2 (Box A3)
    Students
  - "Grant me social recognition or coin to finish my building or I will bite." Cartoon, City Argus., P195; 13 3/4 x 20 3/4 (Box C4)
    Politics
  - Leland Stanford resigns from the presidency of the Southern Pacific Company. City Argus., 1890; P196 (Box A3)
  - Stanford vs. California, football, annual inter-collefgiate game. Saturday, November 14, 1903. S.F. ? Louis Roesch Co., Ltd., 1903.; Gift of David Kalkbrenner, Palo Alto, January 1978., Nov. 14, 1903; P197; 13 x 20 (Box C4)
    Football -- big game
  - "A fitting successor to Lincoln," City Argus, April 28, 1888. Illustration presuming Stanford's candidacy for the republican nomination for president., P198; 20 1/2 x 13 1/2 (Box C4)
  - University de Leland Stanford Jr. (California) American Architecht an building news, July 15, 1893, no.916. Quadrangles different from actual. Gift of Franklin O. Rose, 1970., P203.1; 13 1/2 x 36 (Box MC)
    Campus Plan - 1893
  - "The last and only warning of the '23 class to the unorganized rabble of the FROSH.. ." Frosh-Soph tie-up poster, 1921., P203.2; 37 x 22 (Box MC)
    Student life -- Frosh-Soph Tie Up
  - Stanford Honor Code, 1931. "Posted by request of the Associated Students of Stanford University." Gift of Reid Briggs, 1978., P204; 10 x 12 1/2 (Box A3)
    Associated Students of Stanford University
  - Principal and Trustees of Antioch Public Schools: certificate of honor awarded to Elwood P. Cubberley, champion of locution., Feb. 22, 1878; P205.1 (Box A3)
    Cubberley, E. P.; Cubberley, Elwood Patterson
  - Indiana University: Bachelor of Arts in Physics, awarded to Elwood P. Cubberley, June 1891. Signed by Indiana president, David Starr Jordan., P205.2; diploma (Box C4)
    Cubberley, Elwood Patterson; Cubberley, E. P.
  - Columbia University, teachers college: Masters Diploma in Education awarded to Elwood P. Cubberly, 1902., P205.3; diploma (Box C4)
  - Columbia University: Masters in art awarded to Elwood P. Cubberly, 1902., P205.4; diploma (Box C4)
  - Columbia University, teachers college: Doctorate Diploma in Education awarded to Elwood P. Cubberly, 1905., P205.5; diploma (Box C4)
  - Columbia University: Doctorate of Philosophy awarded to Elwood P. Cubberly, 1905., P205.6; diploma (Box C4)
  - Columbia University: Butler Silver Medal for Competance in Educational Theory awarded to Elwood P. Cubberly, 1915., P205.7 (Box C4)
  - Panama-Pacific International Exposition: commemorative medal of bronze for distinguished service awarded to Elwood P. Cubberly, 1915., P205.8 (Box C4)
  - Pi Gamma Mu: membership certificate of Elwood P. Cubberly., 1926; P205.9 (Box A3)
  - National Education Association of the United States: active member for life award given to Elwood P. Cubberly, 1933., P205.10 (Box A3)
  - National Education Association of the United States: Honorary life membership awarded to Elwood P. Cubberly, 1933. Also, letter re: Cubberly's membership from William G. Carr to Jesse B. Sears, Dec 13, 1954., P205.11 (Box C4)
  - Columbia University: The University Medal awarded to Elwood P. Cubberly, 1933., P205.12 (Box C4)
  - Indiana University: honorary Doctorate of Laws awarded to Elwood P. Cubberly, 1934., P205.13; diploma (Box C4)
  - State University of Iowa: honorary Doctorate of Laws awarded to Elwood P. Cubberly, 1934., P205.14 (Box C4)
  - Commemoration of "The Master Craftsman's Quater Century of Stanford Service" awarded to Elwood P. Cubberly, and the establishment of the Cubberly Anniversary Fund., 1-Jun-23; P205.15 (Box C4)
  - Fire Department. Leland Stanford Junior University seal sticker used on University fire trucks, 197?, P206; hand painted with gummed backing; 10 in. diameter (Box A3)
    Univeristy Seals; Fire Department
  - Hodgel, Theodore. Stanford campus. Etching; artist's proof. Image reversed., 1968; P207; etching; 13 1/4 x 18 1/2 (Box B3)
    campus views; Hodgel, Theodore; Hodgel, Theodore
  - The Stanford Collection. Portfolio of 16 color reproductions of art works originally done in watercolors and photographs showing campus scenes. Published by the Alumni Association., 1940; P208 (Box A3)
    campus views; Stoll, John; Krummel, Leopold; Hook, Kenneth; Stephens, Richard; Crandall, Burton; Roberts, Howard
  - The California wonder Occident, owned by Gov. Leland Stanford. -- New York: Currier & Ives, 1873. Photo historians believe this print was taken from the Edward Muybridge photo, now lost., P209 c. 1; 11 x 16 inches (Box B3)
    Occident;; Palo Alto Stock Farm - Horses
  - Adler, Seon. Stanford quad circa 1905. -- [Palo Alto]: Seon Adler, 1980. Limited edition print from original pencil drawing; number 60 of 75., P210a; 11 x 14 (Box B3)
    Quad;; Memorial Arch; Adler, Seon; Adler, Seon
  - Adler, Seon. Entrance gates on Palm Drive, Stanford University, circa 1905. --[Palo Alto]: Seon Adler, 1980. Limited edition print from origianl pencil drawing; number 60 of 75., P210b; 11 x 14 (Box B3)
    Palm Drive - Entrance Gates; Adler, Seon; Adler, Seon
  - Japanese caligraphy wall hanging. On permanent loan to Okada House, Wilbur Hall., 1937; P211
    On permanent loan to Okada House, Wilbur Hall. December, 1980. Carolyn McCane Chin.